Guide to the Cornell Theory Center Visualization Group files, 1988-2008.
Cornell Theory Center Visualization Group files
- Videos
  - NIH Symposium Day 2 - 5: Charles Brooks (Scripps), 2000; V-1397 (Box 9)
  - NIH Symposium Day 2 - 6: David Beveridge (Wesleyan), 2000; V-1398 (Box 9)
  - NIH Symposium Day 2 - 7: Jiali Gao, 2000; V-1399 (Box 9)
  - NIH Symposium Day 2 - 8: John Moult (Carb/NIST), 2000; V-1400 (Box 9)
  - Tom Coleman: Intro to Discrete Hedging 020321, 2002; V-1401 (Box 9)
  - Saveh Elmohamed: MPI Persistent Communication, 2000; V-1402 (Box 9)
  - Susan Mehringer: Batch/CCS, 2000; V-1402 (Box 9)
  - Daniel Sverolik: Parallel Programs, 2000; V-1402 (Box 9)
  - Daniel Sverolik: Collective Communication, 2000; V-1403 (Box 9)
  - Slava Zaloj: Point -to-Point Communication, 2000; V-1403 (Box 9)
  - John Zollweg: Derived Data, 2000; V-1403 (Box 9)
  - Steve Lantz: Collective communication II, 2000; V-1403 (Box 9)
  - Linda Buttel: Intro to MPI, 2000; V-1403 (Box 9)
  - Gerd Heber: Benchmarks, 2002; V-1404 (Box 9)
  - Gerd Heber: Face Shot, 2002; V-1404 (Box 9)
  - Gerd Heber: Over the Shoulder Shot to Laptop, 2002; V-1404 (Box 9)
  - Gerd Heber: Benchmarks, 2002; V-1405 (Box 9)
  - Gerd Heber: Laptop Visual, 2002; V-1405 (Box 9)
  - Gerd Heber: Benchmarks, 2002; V-1406 (Box 9)
  - Gerd Heber: Laptop Visual, 2002; V-1406 (Box 9)
  - John Zollweg Partner Training 1: MPI Lectures 1, 2003; V-1407 (Box 9)
  - John Zollweg Partner Training 2: MPI Lectures 2, Parallel Programming, 2003; V-1408 (Box 9)
  - John Zollweg Partner Training 3: MPI Lectures, Benchmark, 2003; V-1409 (Box 9)
  - Lifka Partner Training 1: Intro to HPC at CTC, Module 1, HPC Cluster Computing, 2003; V-1410 (Box 9)
  - Lifka Partner Training 2: Module 1b, Killer APPS; Module 3, Research Management + Scheduling, 2003; V-1411 (Box 9)
  - Lifka Partner Training 3: Module - HW Design, 2003; V-1412 (Box 9)
  - Partner Training Will Law: end of lecture: Building a Windows HPC, 2003; V-1413 (Box 9)
  - Partner Training Will Law 2: Core Components of a Windows HPC Cluster, 2003; V-1414 (Box 9)
  - Will Law, 2003; V-1415 (Box 9)
  - Lucy Walle: Tips on Blog HPC Cluster, 2003; V-1416 (Box 9)
  - Jarek Pillardy: Computational Biology on HPC, 2003; V-1416 (Box 9)
  - Drew Dolgert: Benchmarks in Practice, 2003; V-1416 (Box 9)
  - Gerd Heber Compound Fracture on HPC, 2003; V-1416 (Box 9)
  - Paul Redfern: CTC Partner Case Examples, 2003; V-1417 (Box 9)
  - Roger Lang Partner Training 1: CTC as Partner, 2003; V-1417 (Box 9)
  - Roger Lang Partner Training 2: Partnering with CTC, 2003; V-1418 (Box 9)
  - Rana Morris: NCBI Lecture 1, 2004; V-1419 (Box 9)
  - Rana Morris, Eric Sayers: NCBI Lecture 2, 2004; V-1420 (Box 9)
  - Eric Sayers: NCBI Lecture 3, 2004; V-1423 (Box 9)
  - Andrei Gabrielian: NCBI Lab 1, 2004; V-1424 (Box 9)
  - Andrei Gabrielian: NCBI Lab 2, 2004; V-1425 (Box 9)
  - Gerd Heber: Polycrystal 1, 2004; V-1426 (Box 9)
  - Gerd Heber: Polycrystal 2, 2004; V-1427 (Box 9)
  - Scoy People; Cave Demo, 2004; V-1428 (Box 9)
  - Mike Veilleux: Draft Talking Head for DARPATECH, 2007; V-1429 (Box 9)
  - Mike Veilleux, Andy Liu, Ken Ridley, Jeff Bozek: Stereoscopic Experiments for DARPATECH, 2007; V-1430 (Box 9)
  - Ken Ridley, Mike Veilleux, Andy Liu, Jeff Bozek: Stereoscopic Experiments for DARPATECH, 2007; V-1431 (Box 9)
- Digital Audio Tapes
  - Twinning Narration: Paul Dawson, 9-23-97, 1997; tr8282d (Box 9)
  - Paul Dawson: narration for "Polycrystals"[?], tr8283d (Box 9)
  - Texturing of Rock Narration, 1996; tr8284d- tr8285d (Box 9)
- 2"x2" Slides (masters)
  - Tsunami, Catherine, 1992-1993; 1 (Box 10)
  - Bollen's Comet; Catherine, 1989-1992; 1-3 (Box 10)
  - Zooplankton, Chuck Green, 1992-1993; 3-4 (Box 10)
  - Galaxy evolution, Gelb, 1989; 4-5 (Box 10)
  - Ozone, Quartz, Diamond, Benzene; Assamey Teter, 1989-1991; 5-7 (Box 10)
  - Eyeball with scan beam, Wayne, 1989-1991; 7-8 (Box 10)
  - Ink jet, Wayne, 1989; 8-9 (Box 10)
  - Legos, Wayne, 1991-1992; 9-10 (Box 10)
  - More bells and whistles, Wayne, 1990-1992; 10 (Box 10)
  - Phobos, Wayne, 1991-1992; 10-11 (Box 10)
  - Publicity, Wayne, 1989-1990; 11 (Box 10)
  - Pulsar, Wayne, 1992; 11-12 (Box 10)
  - Kidney, Wang, 1992-1993; 12 (Box 10)
  - Brian Wyvill, 1989; 12-13 (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous, 1990-1993; 13-14 (Box 10)
  - Unidentified, 2000; 14-15 (Box 10)